eurojobs.com 2006-06-21

# Privacy Statement

|   |   
---|---  
  
Register  
---  
1\. If you have aready registered please  
click here.  
2\. If you have not registered previously please click here.  
Registration will enable you to benefit form the Eurojobs advanced CV submission and application interface.   
  |   
---|---  
  
My CV  
---  
Submit your CV by enterring your details into our online form, you can also attach a covering letter and a current photograph.  
Please note: Candidates cannot apply for jobs without a CV.  
  |   
---|---  
  
My Jobs  
---  
Manage your Job seeking process: exchange comments with the recruiters, check your place in the recruitment process, apply directly for jobs, respond to offers and more.  
  |   
---|---  
  
Edit Details  
---  
Change your registration details. e.g. change your password. To maintain your security.  
  |   
---|---  
  
My Searches  
---  
Holds any saved vacancy searches you may wish to repeat - As your job requirements often do not change but advertised vacancies do. Edit / remove saved searches.  
  |   
---|---  
  
MailBot  
---  
Auomatically receive notification by email of new jobs that match your desired parameters.  
  |   
---|---  
  
Privacy Settings  
---  
Automatically hide specific information from recruiters. You control what they see. e.g. your current employer.  
  |   
---|---  
  
  |   
---|---  
  
Register  
---  
1\. If you have aready registered please  
click here.  
2\. If you have not registered previously please click here.  
Registration will enable you to post Job Adverts, browse candidates and manage your search and selection processes.   
  |   
---|---  
  
Post Advert  
---  
Post Job Adverts as and when required. Post jobs in multiple countries. Attach your logo to personalise your adverts.  
  |   
---|---  
  
Campaign Manager  
---  
Separate your Job Adverts by campaign. Review all applicants by advert. Communicate with candidates, manage their progress through the selection process.  
  |   
---|---  
  
Search CVs  
---  
Actively seek candidates to match to your Job adverts. Review their CV summary before purchase.  
Search by Job Title, Sector, Country or by using using multiple keywords for qualifications and desription information.  
  |   
---|---  
  
CV Manager  
---  
Search, purchase and review specific Candidate CVs. Match our Candidates to your Jobs.  
  |   
---|---  
  
Subscribe  
---  
Purchasing a 12 month subscription to EuroJobs entitles you to post unlimited Job adverts in text or HTML formats.   
Your organistation will also be entered into our EuroPages online directory, together with an active email address and an optional website link.  
  |   
---|---  
  
Edit Details  
---  
Change your registration details. e.g. change your password. Maintain your security.  
  |   
---|---  
  
  |   
---|---  
  
|  |  |  | We Protect Your Right to Privacy   
Eurojobs.com is vigilant about protecting your privacy. As an on-line recruitment company, we understand better than most the need for you to maintain control over your personal data when using the Internet. We maintain your privacy through the enforcement of strict internal polices that exceed industry standards. We try to be as transparent as possible, so you can always see and act upon what is being done with your data. |   
---|---  
Our guidelines for protecting the information you provide us during a visit to our Web site appear below. |    
Privacy Statement   
This statement discloses the privacy practices for www.Eurojobs.com. We have designed Eurojobs.com so that no personal identifying information is displayed online or is accessible to the general public. |    
What Information We Gather/Track   
We collect and store some or all of the following information about our users: name; email address; and billing information, such as address, phone number and CV details. Eurojobs does not store credit card details. We also receive and may store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Eurojobs.com.  |    
In order to tailor our subsequent communications to you and continuously improve our products and services (including registration), we may also ask you to provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experience with our services, and more detailed contact preferences. You will have the option of choosing not to provide us with this information. |    
Use of Data   
Eurojobs.com uses your information to better understand your needs and provide you with better service. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction, including fulfillment of promotional offers, to communicate back to you, to update you on service and benefits, to personalize our web sites for you, and to manage and renew your subscription(s). Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and fraud protection, and are not used for other purposes without your permission.  |    
Web Applications    
Certain online applications, such as the various elements of the Eurojobs.com, store some components on your hard drive. The software employs proprietary technology to scan your computer system and retrieve information regarding your installed software and hardware. The information that is retrieved is used to provide the services you have chosen to subscribe to or use. In addition, unless you indicate you do not want this service, the information will be used to generate advertising that is appropriate for you. The information gathered by these applications is used only to generate output directed to you and is not aggregated or used for any other purpose. It is not stored along with any identifying information about you, nor is it sold, rented, or shared with any outside parties in any form whatever. |    
Use of Your Email Address   
If you provide us with your email address when you register as a customer or make a purchase from us, we will occasionally send you email with recommendations or notices of new products, prices, and services. This email may include paid advertisements from third parties. You may block future email of this type, simply by following the instructions at the bottom of the update messages. |    
Separately, we send service notifications via email to keep you informed about the status of your service orders or accounts and to provide updates and technical notices. These messages are essential to the maintenance of your subscription and the functionality of our services. Therefore there is no opt-out available for service notifications and these messages cannot be blocked. |    
Who We Share It With   
Eurojobs.com will not sell, rent, or lease your personally identifiable information to others. Unless we have your permission or are required by law, we will only share the personal data you provide online with other Eurojobs.com entities and/or business partners who are acting on our behalf for the uses described in "Terms of Use". By contract, third parties must comply with their own privacy policies with regard to the renting, selling, or sharing of information. As partners of Eurojobs.com, they must also offer Eurojobs.com customers the chance to opt out of information sharing. For advertising purposes, visitor and customer information is statistically aggregated and reported to advertisers. However, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to personally identify you, such as your name, email address, account, password, or transaction history.  |    
Special Relationships   
Eurojobs.com has a number of relationships with business partners. These business partners provide a number of different services. |    
Ferguson Walsh is a network of independently owned search and selection consultants in Europe and provide face-to-face search and selection services to eurojobs subscribers. e-Clear provides credit card transaction services for Eurojobs.com.com. The Bank of Scotland provides electronic check processing services for Eurojobs.com. Both e-Clear and the Bank of Scotland verify your purchase information, such as credit card number or checking account number, and authorize your transaction. In doing so, e-Clear and the Bank of Scotland have access to sensitive data about users. They do not use this information for any other purpose.  
[Read Bank of Scotland's privacy policy](http://www.bos.com/). |    
Pump Internet powers the Eurojobs.com shopping software, and in doing so collects information about users, including credit card information. When a user purchases a product or service from Eurojobs.com, information about the customer and the purchase are shared with Eurojobs.com. Eurojobs.com may occasionally notify you of special offers, new products, services, promotions, and other similar information. Eurojobs.com users can opt out of receiving such mail by calling +44 1260 224014 and asking to be removed from future emails or unsubscribe on-line. [Read Eurojobs' privacy policy](http://drhome.digitalriver.com/livehtml/newsite/dr_privacy_000.html).  |    
Links ****  
Eurojobs.com contains links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are 'clicking' to another Web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites, as their privacy policies may differ from ours. |    
Log Files   
Eurojobs.com maintains log files of the traffic that visits the Eurojobs.com site. We do not link any information gathered in these log files to personally identifying information. Log files are used to manage traffic loads and information technology requirements for providing reliable service. Information collected includes IP addresses and browser types. |    
**Feedback**   
We collect user feedback. We do not typically respond to user feedback in the form of email. We do collect testimonials that appear on the site from our feedback form, but only after we have obtained permission from the senders. Users who would like a response to specific questions concerning the service or their subscriptions are directed to the customer service area. These questions will be answered as quickly as possible. We read all of our customer service queries and use the information contained therein only to resolve the question at hand. We also post surveys on our site, ranging from one to ten questions. These surveys are optional and all information is collected anonymously. The information is collected to better understand our user population. It is not sold or transferred to any third party.  |    
Correct/Update/Delete User Information   
Users can update, correct, or delete their personal information on Eurojobs.com by clicking on the "My Account" link on any page.  |    
How to Contact Us   
Privacy Coordinator   
www.eurojobs.com Ltd  
Heathfield House  
303 Tarring Road  
Worthing  
West Sussex BN11 5JG  
United Kingdom  
Tel: +44 1260 223144  
Fax: +44 1260 223145  
Information Security   
All information gathered on the Eurojobs.com site is stored and maintained in secure facilities that limit access to authorized personnel only. This personnel can only access the information through a series of access-control procedures. All Eurojobs.com employees are briefed about the company's privacy and security policies on a regular basis. The Eurojobs.com Web site is regularly tested for security breaches to ensure that all information collected is secure from unauthorized viewing. |    
Notification of Changes   
If we change our privacy policy, we will post a notice on our site so our users are aware of the change in what information we collect, how we use it, and/or under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their previously submitted information in this different manner. Users may choose to have their information used in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. |    
  |
